Earthstorm is a tv movie, action, science fiction
film directed by Terry Cunningham.
A massive asteroid impact on the moon begins causing storms on
earth due to the sudden changes in ocean tides.
But when further examination is conducted it's discovered that the moon's
structure is now entirely unstable -- threatening all life on earth.
With time running out, a team of scientists turn to one man, demolitions expert
John Redding, in effort to find a solution and secure the moon.
John Redding, played by Stephen Baldwin.
Dr. Lana Gale, played by Amy Price-Francis.
Dr. Garth Bender, played by John Ralston.
Victor Stevens, played by Dirk Benedict.
Albert, played by Matt Gordon.
Bryna, played by Anna Silk.
Matt Gordon (born 1969) is a Canadian actor, best known for playing Doc in the sports sitcom
Rent-a-Goalie, and for his portrayal of Officer Oliver Shaw in the drama series Rookie Blue.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.